https://silktide.com/solutions/data-privacy/

Skip to main content
Solutionsprotect your brandWeb accessibilityTest against WCAG 2.1Content optimizationDeliver better contentGDPREnsure GDPR complianceUptime monitorCheck your site is onlinegrow your reachSEOImprove visibility onlineMobileTest on every deviceUser experienceSupercharge your siteplatform featuresInspectorSee all issues in-situPoliciesAdd custom test criteriaPrioritizationFix important issuesLearning resourcesEducate your teamIntegrationsConnect your CMSSell your digital marketing services with Silktide ProspectIndustriesGovernmentHigher educationPrivate sectorWeb agenciesFinancialResourcesBlogSupportSilktide IndexAccessibility bookToolsWebinarsCase studies
Sign in
Request demo
Solutionsprotect your brandWeb accessibilityTest against WCAG 2.1Content optimizationDeliver better contentGDPREnsure GDPR complianceUptime monitorCheck your site is onlinegrow your reachSEOImprove visibility onlineMobileTest on every deviceUser experienceSupercharge your siteplatform featuresInspectorSee all issues in-situPoliciesAdd custom test criteriaPrioritizationFix important issuesLearning resourcesEducate your teamIntegrationsConnect your CMSIndustriesGovernmentHigher educationPrivate sectorWeb agenciesFinancialResourcesBlogSupportSilktide IndexAccessibility bookToolsWebinarsCase studies
Book a demo
Make your website GDPR compliant
Use Silktide to create privacy alerts and monitor GDPR compliance across your websites.
Request demo
See a GDPR report
What is privacy?
Personal data are any information related to an identified or identifiable person. This covers a wide range, including name, address, location, IP address, and cookies.
GDPR impacts websites even if the operating organization has no physical presence in Europe and doesn’t target European customers.
Organizations collecting or processing personal data of EU citizens must comply with GDPR.
What is the potential impact of getting GDPR wrong?
Organizations found to violate GDPR are at risk of a penalty of 4% of global revenue, or €20 million. Data protection authorities can also issue sanctions such as bans on data processing or public reprimands.
Silktide tracks GDPR violations and gives your team a priority list of remedial actions.
Cookie control
Tracking cookies are subject to GDPR legislation. Your privacy policy must outline the cookies used on your site.
Silktide lists all the cookies you’re using and alerts you if new cookies are detected. This enables you to keep your privacy policy up to date.
See cookies in action
Form data
Keep track of website forms that track and collect personally identifiable information.
See it in action
Geographical footprint
Under GDPR, the country holding personal data is significant. Silktide identifies the collection and storage of user data by location so you can audit data privacy by location.
View geographic footprint
Get a free demo
Interested in a free consultation from our friendly experts? Get in touch and we’ll talk through data privacy for your website.
Request demo
